雷 你要去哪里?
Ray, where are you going?
回来睡觉
Come back to bed.
小心点 你这小可怜...
Watch it, you miserable little...
昆妮!
Queenie!
早 瓦特!
'Morning, Walter!
小乖乖 他们的草坪需要养分
早 中尉
Good morning, Lieutenant.
伦斯菲太太
Mrs Rumsfield.
嗨 瑞奇
伦斯菲先生 小心...
Oh, Mr Rumsfield, be careful. Queenie...
该死的
Goddam it.
瓦特
Walter. Walter!
- 瓦特! - 我真爱那老兄
- Walter! - I love that dude.
- 瓦特! - 马克!
- Walter! Walter! - Mark!
你起来干嘛?
What are you doing up?
瓦特的狗又在伦斯菲的草坪上大便了
Walter's dog just took a dump on Rumsfield's lawn again.
很好
Good, honey.
糟老头 我知道你在里面
I know you're in there, old man!
- 邻居听得到了 - 你给我听好
- Honey, honey, the neighbours. - Listen up, mister.
你那只会叫的老鼠这次是最后一次在我的草坪上大便
That piece of scum, barking rat of yours has just taken his last dump on my lawn!
我再发现一次 我就要把它的屁股缝起来
I find one more... just one... I'm gonna catch him and staple his ass shut!
- 我现在就动手 - 亲爱的 别这样
- I'm gonna do it right now. - No, no, no! Honey, don't.
我们回家吧
Come on. Let's go home.
亲爱的 我们应该搬家
Hey, honey, I think we should move.
对面是个军火贩子而那边住着一个疯子
We got an arms dealer across the street and a crazy person down it.
他们没事就吵个没完
All they do is fight.
够甜吗?
Is this sweet enough?
隔壁新搬来的人姓什么?
Now these new next-door neighbours... What is their name?
- 柯罗佩? - 嗯
- The Klopeks? - Mm-hmm.
- 那是斯拉夫的名字吗? - 不知道
- Is that a Slavic name? - I don't know.
他们已经搬来一个月了 你想他们会整理庭院吗?
They've been here a month. Think they're gonna do something about their yard?
你还要吃吗?
Are you gonna eat any of this?
不 我的胃又在痛了
Oh, no. I got that thing with my stomach again.
不知道昨晚那里又在搞什么鬼
I wonder what was going on over there last night.
- 我就知道会这样 - 什么?
- I knew this was gonna happen. - What?
- 没事 - 你知道会发生什么事?
- Nothing. - What did you know was going to happen?
已经开始了
It's started already. Look at you.
你准备就这样坐着发呆一星期
You're gonna sit around all week doing nothing...
回去上班时感觉只会比现在更糟
get bored out of your mind and go back to work worse than you are now.
我才不会
No, I'm not.
求求你 让我们离开家吧 开去湖边休息一下
Please, let's pack up the car and go to the lake. Just get away and rest.
看看你 大清早起来看狗大便
You should see yourself. You were up at dawn watching a dog poop.
你把去湖边叫做休息吗?
You call going up to the lake resting?
在假日的车潮中开四个小时的车
It is four hours of driving on the tollway in holiday traffic...
就为了去某间潮湿的小屋
to sit in some dank, wet cabin...
然后等着隔壁的大头喝醉 从楼梯跌下去
and wait for that neighbour with the enormous head to get drunk and fall down.
他得了水脑症 你不应该这样取笑他
He's a hydrocephalic. I don't think that you should make fun of him.
亲爱的 那可不是我心目中的休息
Honey, that's not my idea of restful.
待在家里 什么也不做 这才叫休息
This is restful: Hanging around the house, just being lazy.
我就要待在家里
That's what I want to do. I just wanna... hang around.
什么也不做 听听球赛
Be lazy, listen to the ball game...
喝个两百瓶啤酒
and drink a couple hundred beers.
偶尔在户外抽根雪茄
Smoke an occasional cigar... outside.
我会修理后院的烤肉架
I'll fix the barbecue in the backyard. I'll do that.
卡罗 这正是我想要的
This is what I need, Carol. I need... this.
等着瞧 一周之后我就会脱胎换骨
And at the end of the week, I'll be a brand new human being.
反正这是你的休假
It's your vacation.
【文森】
嘘! 安静点
Shh! Quiet.
阿特拿着枪
Art's got a gun.
阿特!
Art!
雷 你们在吃饭吗?
Hey, hi, Ray. Are you guys eatin' in there?
你知道苏珊对她的喂鸟器很讲究挑剔
You know how Suzette is about her bird feeder.
这些乌鸦不知道从哪里跑出来
These crows start showing up out of nowhere.
她一直念着要我把它们赶走
She's all over my back to get rid of 'em.
她说 乌鸦太大了 用不了喂食器
"The crows are too big for the bird feeder," she says.
- 我不记得以前看过乌鸦 - 坏得很
- I don't remember seeing crows around before. - Oh, big bastards too.
所以我才拿着枪 准备射个几只
That's why I got the gun. I'm gonna pop a few.
你怎么不跟苏珊去她妈妈家?
Why didn't you go with Suzette to her mother's?
嘿 我在这里这里吃饭 你能想像我和她们俩单独相处一星期吗?
Hey, I'm eating here. Can you imagine me and the two of them alone for a week?
我宁愿嚼碎玻璃
I'd rather chew broken glass.
这是单身汉的黄金假期啊
Uh-uh, this is gonna be a big week for the bachelor kid.
文森
Vince.
雷 你怎么没去上班?
How come you're not at work, Ray?
- 我请了一星期的假 - 一星期的休假?
- I took the week off. - A week off?
真好 你们打算去湖边吗?
That's great. Are you guys going to the lake or something?
- 不 后院 - 后院?
- No, the backyard. - Backyard?
我只想待在家里休息
I just want to hang around the house and relax.
休息? 看看你们隔壁的怪胎 祝你好运
Relax? Good luck with those maniacs you got living next door.
- 你有见过柯罗佩一家人吗? - 没有
- Have you met the Klopeks yet? - No.
我没见过 这条街上没人见过
No, I haven't. Nobody on the block has.
可是我和卖房子给他们的那个女经纪人谈过
But I did talk to the real estate broad that sold them the place.
据说他们上一栋房子被烧了
Apparently, their last house only burnt to the ground.
- 真的吗? - 是啊
- Really? - Yep.
燃烧的恐怖地狱
A hideous, raging inferno.
来自地狱的芳邻
Neighbours from hell.
也许吧
Maybe.
不论如何 我很庆幸我不住在他们隔壁
Whatever it is, I'm glad I'm not the one who lives right next door.
来吧 让我们面对现实 柯罗佩一家很古怪
Come on, let's face it. These Klopeks are strange.
从他们搬来以后我就一直在观察
I've been watching that house ever since they moved in.
没人进来 没人出去
No one goes in. No one comes out.
没有访客 没有送货
No visitors. No deliveries.
你觉得他们都吃什么?
What do you think they're eatin', Ray?
也许这些人只想独来独往
Well, maybe these people just want to keep to themselves, Art.
还记得以前住在隔壁的纳普斯家吗?
Remember when the Knapps lived next door?
你和他们聊过几次? 两次
How many conversations did you have with the Knapps? I had two.
他们搬走时连一声再见也没说
They didn't even say goodbye when they moved.
拜托 这两家根本不能比
Oh, please. Don't even compare the two.
即使纳普斯一家不爱说话也还算正常
At least, if they weren't conversational the Knapps were semi-normal.
他们会整理庭院 会锄草 他们有一块草坪
They worked in their yard. They mowed their lawn. They had a lawn to mow.
至于柯罗佩家... 我们甚至不知道有几口人
These Klopeks... We don't even know how many of them there are.
一共有三人
There are three of them.
只有晚上才会出来
They only come out at night.
瑞奇巴特勒说他们是夜行性动物
Ricky Butler says they're nocturnal feeders.
瑞奇巴特勒说的
Oh, Ricky Butler says.
上星期我拿着望远镜爬上屋顶
Last week when I was up on the roof with my telescope...
看到他们在自己的后院
I saw them in their backyard.
- 他们在做什么? - 挖地
- What were they doing, honey? - Digging.
- 像挖墓者吗? - 有可能
- Kind of like grave diggers? - Maybe.
好了 谈话到此为止
All right, that's enough of this conversation.
我不准你再和瑞奇巴特勒偷窥柯罗佩家了
I want you to stop spying on the Klopeks with Ricky Butler.
还有我不希望你在他脑袋里灌输这些半调子理论
And I'd like you to stop filling his head with such half-cocked theories.
- 你要去哪里? - 去换上我的休假拖鞋
- Where you goin'? - I'm gonna change into my vacation togs.
蛋吃完了吗?
Are you done with your eggs?
我要把百日菊和其他花混在一起
I'm gonna mix the zinnias in with the rest of the flowers.
苗圃的人说...
The man at the nursery said...
- 真把我气死了 - 什么?
- Boy, that really burns my ass. - What?
那个老烂人 他的草坪是这条街最漂亮的
That old fart. He's got the best lawn on the block.
你知道为什么吗?
And you know why?
因为他训练小狗在我的院子大便
Because he trains his dog to crap in my yard.
嘿 伦斯菲太太
Hey, Mrs Rumsfield.
今天早上没有晒黑线
No tan lines this morning.
很俏
Looks nice.
隔壁那个小子真没出息
That kid next door is a meatball.
彼得森
Peterson.
昨天晚上那群外国佬吵吵闹闹时 他穿着睡袍走出来
He came out in his robe last night when the foreigners were making that racket.
什么也没做
He didn't do one thing.
你要先做什么?
So, what are you gonna do first?
不晓得
I don't know.
- 我有给你看过我的新工具吗? - 还没
- Hey, did I show you my new tools? - No.
这工具真棒
These are great.
卡罗父亲送我的圣诞节礼物
Carol's father gave them to me for Christmas.
- 你看 - 噢 真帅
- Look. - Oh, those are beauties.
- 要拿它们盖东西吗? - 应该会吧
- You gonna build something with those? - I think so. Probably
球赛什么时候开始?
Hey, what time does the ball game go on?
大概一点吧
I think it's at about 1:00.
你想去小吃店买个牛肉三明治吗?
You want to go down to the deli and get one of those beef sandwiches?
不想 我要去买车库门的电动开关来装
No. I'm thinking of getting one of those electric garage door openers And installing
it.
雷
Ray. Ray!
雷 过来
Ray, come here.
那是什么?
What is it?
是我的邻居
It's my neighbour.
一个匈奴人从洞穴走出来了
Hey, one of the Huns came out of the cave.
去打声招呼吧
Why don't you go say hi?
是呀 何不呢?
Well, yeah, I guess I could.
这个时机最恰好
This would be the perfect time.
如果你去和他搭讪 我们就能知道他是什么德行了 去吧
If you go talk to him, we could see what he's like. Go.
你也可以跟他打招呼啊
You could say hi to him too.
- 可是他是你的邻居 - 他也是你的邻居
- But he's your neighbour. - No, he's your neighbour as well.
可是你的房子和他交界
But you share a property line with him.
我们都在同一条街上 所以你也可以去
We're all on the same block, so you could go too.
我们都在同一个小镇 可是你在他隔壁
We're all in the same town, but you're next to him.
如果他要借东西 他会找你
If he was gonna borrow anything, he'd come over to your place.
他现在很忙
Well, he's busy now.
他才不忙 他要进去了 快点 因为...
He's not busy. Now he's goin' in. Go now because if...
他要进去了 要打招呼就趁现在
He's going back in. If you were gonna say hi, you should probably...
他要进屋子了 你要错过了
He's going into the house. You're gonna lose him.
他要进...
He's gonna go in...
- 现在你搞砸了 - 我才没有搞砸
- Now you've blown it, haven't you? - No, I didn't blow it.
- 胆小鬼 - 他进屋子了
- Chicken. Chicken. - He went into his house.
他走进屋子 又不是我胆小
I'm not chicken because he went into his house.
你在自己儿子面前没种
You look like a chicken in front of your son and everything. Your son.
过来
Come on.
- 如果真的那么了不起 那我们就去打招呼 - 我是开玩笑的
- If it's suddenly a big deal, let's just go say hello. - Hey, hey, it's a joke!
- 去打招呼 - 干嘛那么凶?
- Let's say hello. - Why so edgy?
- 走阿 - 试试无咖啡因
- Come on, come on. - Try decaf.
他们正在看谁有种去按门铃
They're daring each other to ring the doorbell.
我们不应该这样盯着人瞧
We shouldn't stare like this.
我们一起去打招呼 否则你就是胆小鬼
Why don't we both go say hello, or are you chicken?
加油 彼德森先生!
Go for it, Mr Peterson! Yes!
现在大家都在看我们
Now everybody's watching us.
- 干得好! - 好 好吧!
- Good going, man! - Yeah, okay, yeah.
我和你去就是了 没问题
I'll go in with you. Sure. No problem.
走吧
Let's go.
地下室的窗户有铁条
There's bars on the basement windows.
- 他们的阳台也有洞 -那是诱敌的陷阱
- They got holes in their porch too. - That was a booby trap.
- 你还好吧? - 还好
- You okay? - Yeah.
- 我不会付帐的 - 我们应该告他们
- I'm not gonna pay for that. - We shouldn't pay for that. We should sue them.
这个吗... 让我们先打声招呼
Well, um, let's... Let's say hello.
快去拿水管 撑着点!
Get the hose. Hang on, men!
跑来我这! 向水这里跑!
Run to me! Run to water!
雷 过来! 向水这里跑!
Ray, over here! Run to water!
跑来我这! 快!
Run to me! Come on!
我想蜜蜂走了 马克 我想蜜蜂走了!
I think they're gone, Mark. I think they're gone!
- 你们被叮到了吗? - 我不敢相信你们那么做
- You men hit? - I cannot believe you did that.
- 我也不敢相信 - 我不敢相信! 这帅呆了
- Neither can I. - I cannot believe it! That was great.
上星期我去那里也碰到同样的事
The same thing happened to me last week. I was over there.
但不是蜜蜂 而是一只狂犬病的松鼠
It wasn't bees though. It was a foaming squirrel.
在东南亚我们把这种事称为 "业障"
In Southeast Asia, we'd call this type of thing "bad karma."
亲爱的 如果你一直碰 蜜蜂叮的伤口就不会好
Honey, bee stings don't heal if you keep playing with them.
如果我们去湖边 我会被叮两倍的包
If we had gone to the lake, I'd have twice as many of these.
- 你早上可没有什么都说中 - 你要去哪里?
- It isn't like anything you said is coming true. - Where are you going?
我连走到隔壁房间也要你问东问西吗?
I can't walk away without you asking where I'm going?
我要去法国巴黎 我要去加拿大班夫 好吗?
I'm going to Paris, France. I'm going to Banff, Canada, all right?
- 这就是我要去的地方 - 你要带狗去吗?
- That's where I'm going. - Are you taking the dog?
对 对 我要去遛狗
Yeah, yeah. I'm taking the dog for a walk.
不 等等
No, wait, wait, wait.
文森 到这里来
Hey, Vince, let's go over here, huh?
今晚我们不走那条路
Let's not go that way tonight.
这个庭院很好
Here's a nice yard. It's a good yard.
嘿 遛狗的人!
Hey, you with the dog!
嘿 别让那只杂种狗到我的草坪 听到没?
Hey, keep that mutt off my lawn, will ya?
很好 自由活动
All right. Have a field day.
他来这里抽雪茄 因为太太不准 他以为我不晓得
He comes here to smoke cigars. His wife won't let him. He doesn't know I know that.
嗨 雷 你好吗?
Hi, Ray. How ya doin', bud?
- 嘿 彼德森先生 - 很高兴见到你
- Hey, there, Mr Peterson. - Good to see you.
- 要打火机吗? - 谢谢
- Wouldn't need a lighter, would you? - Thanks.
- 今晚夜色真美 - 是呀 绿色的天空
- It is a lovely night, isn't it? - Yeah, green sky tonight.
早晨天空发绿 邻居就要警戒
Green sky at morning: Neighbour take warning.
夜晚天空发绿呢?
Green sky at night?
邻居就该落荒而逃
Neighbour take flight.
彼德森先生 你看过「哨兵」这部电影吗?
Did you ever see the movie The Sentinel, Mr Peterson?
是关于一个老人有一栋...
It's about the old guy who owned the apartment...
像是地狱入口的公寓
which is kind of like the gateway to hell.
我没看过
No, I didn't see that.
我正在想
Oh, well, I was doing some thinking.
他们上一栋房子被烧掉等等的...
And, you know, being that their last house burned down and all...
也许有人把门开着没关
it's like, maybe, somebody left the gate open.
是他们 又在活动了
It's them. They're movin' around again.
事情发生的当晚也是这样
It was a night just like this that it happened.
发生什么了 韦嘉纳先生?
What happened, Mr Weingartner?
那是好久以前的事了 星克立丘那时比现在小多了
It was a long time ago. Hinkley Hills was a lot smaller then.
也比较安全 不必锁门 左邻右舍都认识
Safer too. You never had to lock your doors. Everybody knew everybody.
我那时大概九、十岁吧
I must have been maybe nine, ten years old.
- 你知道现在那个购物中心吧? - 知道
- You know where the big mall is? - Yeah.
街角那里本来是一家杂货店
There used to be a big drugstore on the corner there.
- 有个很大的汽水吧台 记得吗? - 记得
- It had a big soda fountain. Remember? - Yeah.
店主是一个戴着眼镜 矮矮胖胖的人
The guy who ran it was a rotund guy, had glasses.
叫做史奇普 住在榆木街
His name was Skip. Lived over on Elm.
有太太和两个孩子 人不太灵光
Had a wife, a couple kids. Not too sharp.
大概四十岁左右 戴着一顶纸帽子做樱桃可乐
The guy's 40 years old, he's wearing a paper hat and making cherry Cokes.
当然他没有去选州长
It's a cinch he's not running for governor, right?
不管怎样 那年夏天非常闷热
Anyway, it got hot that summer. It got real hot. It was sweltering.
热到连内裤都会出汗 然后爬到...
That heat where your underwear sweats and it crawls up the...
反正很热就对了
Anyway, it's hot, okay?
榆木街开始传出一股臭味
And they start smelling this really vile stench over on Elm...
人们认为是从史普奇家里传出来的
and they figure it's comin' from Skip's place.
没有人想说什么
No one wants to say anything.
难不成趣敲他家的门说 "你家真臭" ?
Do you knock on the guy's door, "Hi, your house stinks"?
所以大家设法不闻不问
So people are trying to ignore it, right?
假装没这回事 你知道那些松香片吧?
They're trying to pretend it isn't happening. You know those pine things?
他们设法用挂在车里的松香片挂在家里的阳台上
They're trying to cover up with those pine things that you can put in cars.
来掩盖那股臭味
People are hanging those on their porches.
- 瑞奇 你觉得很好笑吗? - 是呀
- Oh, you think that's funny, Ricky? - Well, yeah.
让我告诉你后来发生的事
Let me tell you what happened next.
州政府的卫生督察员来到小镇
The state health inspector shows up. They talk to Skip.
和史奇普谈话 他说他的污水帮浦有问题 他们就走了
He says he's got a sump pump problem. They leave.
他说他会想办法修理污水帮浦
The guy's got a sewer problem. He says he'll look after it.
一切都没事了 对吧?
Everything's okay, right?
错了 两个小时后...
Wrong. A couple hours later...
史奇普的窗户开始冒烟
there's smoke pouring out of the windows of Skip's house.
- 救火员赶到 你猜他们发现什么? - 什么?
- The firemen go in. Know what they find? - What?
史奇普的家人 全死了...
Skip's family, dead. Murdered...
好几星期前被史奇普拿冰钻打死了
by Skip... weeks earlier... with an ice pick.
那个人拿着冰钻杀了全家
Yeah, the guy killed his whole family... With an ice pick.
是呀 他把他们放在阴凉的地下室
Yeah. Yeah, just put 'em in the cool basement...
用床单盖着 然后继续为镇上的人做冰淇淋
covered 'em up with a sheet and went back to makin' treats for the townsfolk.
只是史奇普没料到那年夏天热浪来袭
Only Skip didn't count on there being a big heat wave that summer.
你知道镇上的人在榆木街上闻到的是什么味道吗?
You know what all those people were smelling on Elm, Ricky?
是什么?
What?
史奇普家人的尸体在暑气中分解
Skip's family's bodies decomposing in the summer heat.
显然 有一天史奇普多做了一杯柠檬果汁汽水
Apparently, one day Skip made just one-too-many lemon phosphates.
"疯狂杀戒"
El snappo.
我还记得 小时候听人说过
I remember that. I remember hearing about that when I was a kid.
那年夏天他们把汽水吧台拆了
They-They tore down the soda fountain that fall.
这些小镇充满了这一类的故事 就在你的鼻子底下发生
These towns are full of those stories. They're happening right under your nose.
说到鼻子...
You know, speaking of noses...
自从这家人搬来以后...
ever since this family has moved to this block...
我一直闻到一种奇怪的味道
I've been noticing a weird kind of odour.
有点像死尸的味道
Kind of like death.
球员韦布 跳高一点
Jump a little higher, Spud Webb.
- 灌篮高手! - 抱歉 彼德森先生 这是我的错
- Oh, slam dunk! - Sorry, Mr Peterson. It was a mistake.
- 这是我的错 - 别道歉
- Well, it wasn't a mistake. - Don't apologize.
- 我要回家了 - 噢 别这样
- I'm goin' home. - Oh, come on.
- 别这么胆小 只是开个玩笑嘛 - 很抱歉 彼德森先生
- Don't be a weenie. It was a joke! - I'm sorry, Mr Peterson.
我要去做有建设性的事 像是去看电视
I'm gonna go do something productive. I'm gonna go watch television.
答案是 他是华盛顿诞辰后的下一个联邦假日
The answer is: it's the next federal holiday after washington's birthday
- 林肯诞辰
- What is Lincoln's birthday.
- 阵亡将士纪念日? - 阵亡将士纪念日 选择
- What is Memorial Day? - Memorial Day is it. Select.
他们把林肯和华盛顿的诞辰放在同一周
They combined Lincoln's birthday with Washington's. It's one weekend now.
保持镇静 张开双臂 和身体保持正确角度浮起来
"Remain calm, float with arms stretched out at right angles to the body..."
大学时你常对我那样说
That's what you used to say to me in college, right?
- 你父母怎么了? - 他们星期四才回来
- What about your parents? - They're not home 'til Thursday.
吉儿 我对天发誓 这比电视上的节目还精采
Gail, I swear to God, this is better than anything on television.
- 我们为什么不能去看电影? - 电影?
- Why can't we go to a movie? - "A movie"?
那又不是真的 跟电视一样
That's not real. It's the same as television.
相信我 这是真的
Trust me. This is real.
这是我的左邻右舍
This is my neighbourhood.
他又准时出来了
Here he comes, right on schedule.
天啊 我真爱这条街
God, I love this street.
雷
Ray.
- 什么? - 谁是墨索里尼?
- What? - Who was Mussolini?
"多么甜蜜" 是...
"How sweet it is" was, uh...
- 阿特 我们正在看电视 - 他要做什么?
- Art, we're watching the show. - What does he want?
我不知道 不过我会赶回来看 「终极问题」
I don't know. But I'll be back in time for Final Jeopardy.
好戏开始了 看吧
Okay, the show's started. Check it out.
你看到那个捲发的傢伙吗? 那是彼德森先生
You see the guy with the curly hair? That's Mr Peterson.
他是怀疑论者 人很实际
He's this sceptic. He's basically grounded in reality...
不希望相信他的邻居正在搞鬼
and he doesn't want to believe his neighbours are up to something strange.
因为如果是真的 他就得面对
'Cause if they were, he'd have to deal with it.
现在看那个胖子 那是韦嘉纳先生
Okay, now see the fat guy? That's Mr Weingartner.
他认为柯罗佩真的很邪恶
He thinks the Klopeks are really evil...
他们正在地下室建地牢
and that they're building a dungeon in their basement.
他和伦斯菲先生决定今晚做一点探查
He and Mr Rumsfield decided to do a little snooping tonight.
这一定很精彩
This should be good.
- 这是什么? - 这是红外线望远镜
- What is this? - It's an infrared scope.
狙击手的夜视工具
Snipers use it for night vision.
我们拿它做什么?
What are we gonna do with it?
爬过去查看装了铁条的地下室窗户
Get a look in those barred- up basement windows.
我们不应该这样做
I've been thinking about it. I don't think we should go through with this.
你是胆小鬼吗?
Are you a 'fraidy cat?
我只是觉得太过头了
No, I just think things have gone off the deep end.
红外线夜视望远镜? 接下来要窃听电话吗?
Infrared night vision scopes? What are we gonna do next, tap their phone?
那可以安排
That can be arranged.
最后就剩下在他们前院烧一个十字架
Then all we have to do is burn a cross on their front lawn.
- 安静 - 你听到什么?
- Quiet. - You hear that?
我以为只有我听到
I thought that was just me.
- 那是一种低频率的哼声 - 越来越大声
- It's a low-frequency hum or something. - It's getting louder.
你听
Listen.
那是变压器还是什么的?
Is that a transformer or something?
该死的电力公司
The goddam power company.
可是我不能...从哪里传来的?
But I can't... Where is it coming from?
我知道从哪里传来的
I know where it's coming from.
搞什么鬼啊?
What the hell was that?
部分停电
Brownout.
那味道闻起来好像在煮猫
Smells like they're cooking a goddam cat over there.
- 我要去一探究竟 - 蹲下!
- I'm gonna go find out what exactly... - Get down, get down!
没有车前灯
No headlights.
我可以想像新闻报导说
I can see the news report now:
他们一家很安静 独来独往
"They were a quiet family. Kept pretty much to themselves.
没有人怀疑他们正在搞鬼
No one would have ever suspected them of foul play."
我从来没有看过人把自己的垃圾开到路边
I've never seen anybody drive their garbage to the street...
然后拿一根棍子勐敲乱打
and then bang the hell out of it with a stick.
从来没看过
I've never seen that.
我们应该去看看 垃圾桶里面到底有什么
I say we get a look in those garbage cans.
我可能太小心了 可是那样不是有点可疑?
Call me overly cautious, but don't you think that's a bit suspicious?
在晚上十一点下大雨的时候翻他们的垃圾筒?
The three of us going through their garbage at 11:00 at night in the middle of a rainstorm?
说得对 垃圾跑不了的
Affirmative. That garbage is going nowhere.
明天一早在看也不迟 望远镜还我
I say we wait 'til first light. Scope me.
我要走了
I'm outta here.
下雨延期
Rain delay.
真倒楣
Bummer.
你前天说的半调子理论是什么?
Ray, what was that you were saying the other day about half-cocked theories?
雷 好好睡
Ray... sleep tight.
周三晚上不行 我要打保龄球
No way Wednesday night. I'm in a league.
这场讲习会将改变你的一生 那个人是很棒的治疗师
This seminar could change your life, Vic. The man is a great healer.
我是很棒的保龄球选手 周三晚上要对抗罗西利水电队
And I'm a great bowler. Wednesday night we're taking on Roselli Plumbing.
你应该接触这个人
You should expose yourself to this guy, Vic.
他了解超物理力量
He understands paraphysical forces...
水晶的疗效和按手发功
the healing capabilities of crystals and the laying on of hands.
你想试试按手发功吗?
You wanna try laying on some hands?
收垃圾的 等等!
Wait! Hold it, garbies! Garbies!
收垃圾的 等一下!
Garbagemen! Hold on a minute! Wait a sec!
等等! 你在干什么?
Wait! Wait! Wait! Hold it! What are you doin'?
- 我在清垃圾 - 你疯了吗?
- I'm emptying garbage. - Are you outta your mind?
给我!
Give me that!
- 住手! - 什么也没有
- Hey, cut that out! - There's nothing here.
没有断手断脚
Not a finger, not a nose, nothing!
- 把那个给我 - 拿去
- Give me that. - Here you go.
- 你在干什么? - 你要我帮忙
- What are you doin'? - You asked me to help.
你要打给谁?
Who you calling?
我要打给德凡尼 要他们打小木屋打开
I'm calling the Delvaneys and having them open the cottage.
我才不想去小木屋
No, Carol. I don't want to go to the cottage.
好 大卫和我去 你留在这里当间谍
Fine. Then Dave and I will go and you can stay here and spy.
没问题
Oh, all right. Okay.
- 怎么? 你不高兴了? - 没有 去小木屋啊!
- What? What? Are you sulking now? - No, go up to the cottage!
带大卫去小木屋 留我在家里走来走去
Take Dave and go to the cottage. Leave me to pad around the house.
你成天就和那些傻瓜在街上晃来晃去
"Pad around the house"? All you do is pal around the neighbourhood With those two
chuckleheads.
- 我实在很担心你 - 为什么?
- I am very, very worried about you. - Why?
- 看看你这副样子 - 我什么样子?
- You're acting like... - What am I acting like, Carol?
我就像在休假的人
Like a guy who's on vacation!
- 这才不像在休假 - 我很晚起床
- This is not someone on vacation! - See? I sleep late!
- 那去晒晒太阳啊! - 穿睡衣怎么晒?
- Get a tan then! - In my pyjamas?
我不晓得
Fix the barbecue! I don't know!
你去小木屋把自己晒黑 带大卫一起去
You go to the cottage and get a tan! Take David with you!
我不在乎! 我会吃外卖 我会洗衣服
I don't care! I'll eat takeout! I'll do the laundry myself!
我会吸尘 房子会一尘不染
I'll vacuum the house! It'll be spotless!
阿特把垃圾扔到街上
Art's throwing garbage all over the street.
你妈妈和我正在谈话 如果你... 什么?
Your mom and I are having a conversation! If you... What?
从垃圾车出来! 你发神经吗?
Get out of the truck! Are you nuts?
一定在这里某个地方
Hey, it's gotta be in here somewhere.
最高法庭裁决 一个人的垃圾一到路边
The Supreme Court ruled that a person's garbage...
- 就属于公共领域 - 闭嘴
- is public domain the minute it hits the kerb. - Shut up.
你们有没有碰到一个可能有点湿的超大垃圾袋?
Did you guys pick up a Hefty bag out of that yard that was bulky and probably a little moist?
- 这些人怎么搞的? - 他有权利知道
- What is wrong with these people? - He has a right to know, Vic.
别惹我 嘿 你可以帮我把这傢伙弄走吗?
Don't start up with me. Hey, could you help me get this guy out of here?
怎么回事?
Hey, Art. What's happening?
雷 回来!
No! Ray! Ray, come back here!
只要等一... 我就会... 呀
Just one... I'll be... Yeah.
你的薪水是靠我缴的税
My taxes pay your salary!
我在也不想听你胡言乱语
I don't want to hear any of your bullshit either!
这里的问题是垃圾以及谁来收拾这个烂摊子
The question here is garbage and who picks up this mess.
"谁来收拾这个烂摊子"?
"Who picks up this mess"?
你来收拾这个烂摊子 因为你是收垃圾的
You're gonna pick up the mess because you are a garbageman.
我收的是桶子里的垃圾 不是街上的垃圾
I pick up garbage in cans, not from the street!
雷 这里找不到
Ray, there's nothing in here.
我们把整辆车翻遍了 他们一定掉包了
We practically checked this whole truck. They must have switched on us.
- 联邦调查局? - 不 柯罗佩
- The F.B.I.? - No, the Klopeks.
哎呀 淘气的小狗
Oh, no. Naughty little puppy.
你到马克叔叔的草坪他会不高兴的
Uncle Markie gets very upset when you're on his lawn.
等等 你全身脏兮兮的 而且一直在发抖
Wait a minute. You're all dirty, and you're shaking.
瓦特知道你在外面吗?
I wonder if Walter knows you're outside.
- 在雨中? - 是啊 当时在下雨
- In the rain? - Yeah, it was raining.
- 总共有几个人? - 三个
- There were how many of them? - Well, uh, three.
他们当时在做什么?
And what were they doing?
- 他们在挖地 - 就像挖墓者!
- They were diggin'. - Digging! Like grave diggers!
- 他们是食尸者! - 我可没说
- I told you! They're ghouls! - No, I didn't say that.
他们可能在挖别的东西
They could have been digging for anything.
他们可能在挖大蚯蚓
They could have been digging for night crawlers.
- 大蚯蚓? - 他们是渔夫 他们需要鱼饵
- Night crawlers? - They're fishermen. They need bait.
清醒过来 面对现实吧
Wake up and smell the coffee!
那小子昨晚看到我们趁我们睡觉时爬起来
The kid spotted us last night. When we were sleeping, he got up.
走到垃圾筒旁边 拿起尸体然后...
He went to the garbage can, he took the body and then he...
埋在自己的院子里
He buried him in the backyard.
- 我们走吧 - 这个我喜欢
- Let's get outta here. - I like this.
我讨厌死巷 只有一条出路 而且那些人好怪
I hate cul-de-sacs. There's only one way out, and the people are weird.
赤裸的小姐
Naked ladies.
有人知道瓦特把备用钥匙放在哪里吗?
Does anyone know if Walter left a spare key around anywhere?
他出门时一定忘了喂昆妮
He must have gone away and forgot to feed Queenie.
- 瓦特! - 我希望他没事
- Walter! - I hope nothing happened to him.
- 我们应该打电话叫警察 - 这计划还真好啊
- I think we should call the police. - Oh, good plan, Ray.
我看到那里有动静
I think I see something moving in there.
你怎么进去的?
How did you get in there?
士兵有本事解决难题 进来吧
A soldier's way saves the day. Entrez.
- 真棒 亲爱的 - 真漂亮
- Good, honey. - Beautiful.
瓦特?
Walter?
- 看起来不妙
This doesn't look good.
有挣扎的迹象
There are signs of a struggle here.
电视机开着 椅子翻倒
The TV's still on. Chairs turned over.
我不会说那事挣扎的迹象
I wouldn't say that's a sign of a struggle.
我应该上楼检查一下
I think I should go upstairs and check this out.
也许老傢伙躺在楼上的浴缸里
Maybe the guy's upstairs in a bathtub or something...
脑袋开花 到处都是血
cracked his head open, there's blood everywhere...
楼上的东西都别碰 知道吗?
Just don't touch anything up there, all right?
遵命 彼德森先生
Yes, sir, Mr Peterson.
让我们看看有没有狗食
Let's see if we can find some dog food.
我不喜欢在邻居家里偷偷摸摸的
I don't like this. I don't like snooping around a neighbour's house.
你是说死人的家里?
You mean a dead guy's house?
你想把口袋的东西拿出来吗?
You wanna take that out of your pocket?
- 你可以不偷瓦特家的东西吗? - 有什么差别?
- You wanna not steal that from Walter's house? - Hey, what's the difference?
反正这堆垃圾会流进跳蚤市场
All this junk is gonna end up in a flea market sooner or later.
他可能走得匆忙 把狗忘记了
He might have left in a hurry and forgot about the dog.
留在这里 我去找你的盘子
Okay, stay right here, and we'll find your dish.
正中红心!
Bull's-eye!
什么?
What, what, what?
那里有只死老鼠
A dead rat! There!
亲爱的 那不是老鼠
Honey, that's not a rat.
那是瓦特的假发
That's Walter's toupee.
把假发放在炉子上 真是好位置
Beautiful place to keep a toupee: On the stove.
我饿死了
I'm starving.
我们知道这些老人家
One thing about these old guys:
他们没戴假发是不会出门的
They don't ever leave the house without their hair.
不对
No, sir.
瓦特是在匆忙中离开房子的
Walter left this house in a big hurry.
大伙来看! 这些饼干是...
Hey, you guys, look! These cookies are...
好极了 大家出去!
That's great! Everybody out!
我们在一天之内已经触犯太多法律了
I think we've broken enough laws for one day.
- 抱歉 可是我们没有看... - 离开这里
- Hey, sorry, but we have not looked... - Let's just get outta here.
打破饼干又不犯法
It's not against the law to break cookies.
我不敢相信你竟然说服我这样做
I can't believe you people talked me into this.
我们离开邻居的房子好吗?
Why don't we just get out of our neighbour's house?
瓦特 你的狗在我的家里
Walter, your dog is at my house.
你的窗户破了 因为我们以为...
Your window is broken because we all thought that..."
瓦特... 你的狗在我这里
Walter... I have your dog.
雷
Ray.
柯罗佩先生
Mr Klopek!
柯罗佩先生 我是雷彼德森
Mr Klopek, hi. Ray Peterson.
听好 我是...
Listen, I was w...
这封狗电报写什么? 刚刚送来 可能很重要
What is this doggy-gram? This just came for you. It might be important.
过来 留一点给你的朋友 在那里 来啊
Come here. Save some for your friend. Right there. Go on.
- 甜心 你有看到爸爸吗? - 他跟阿特在地下室
- Honey, have you seen your father? - I think he's in the basement with Art.
在玩纸牌游戏
He's playing canasta or something.
亲爱的?
Honey?
雷!
Ray!
【魔鬼研究的理论与实践】
你梦到你赢了彩劵 结果花了五百元买彩劵
Art, you had a dream you were gonna win the lottery. You blew $500 on tickets.
【魔鬼研究的理论与实践】
我不敢相信你又旧事重提
I can't believe you're still bringing that up.
你梦到飞机坠毁 所以改搭巴士去拉斯维加斯
You had a dream a plane was gonna crash, so you took the bus to Las Vegas.
如果我上了那班飞机 它就会坠毁
If I had been on the plane, it would have crashed.
这不是梦 这事灵视
This wasn't a dream. This was a vision.
这些人是恶魔崇拜者
These people are Satanists. They are Satanists.
一派胡言
This is all gibberish.
听好 世界上这种事情多的是
Look, the world is full of these kind of things. Look at this.
黑弥撒 断手截脚
Black masses, mutilations. Mutilations!
男妖和女魔 我告诉你 瓦特被当成献祭了
The incubus, the succubus. I'm telling you, Walter was a human sacrifice.
我早该去湖边
I should have gone to the lake.
我早该听卡罗的话
I should have listened to Carol.
听你太太的话? 谁会听自己太太的? 你一定要听我说
Listen to your wife? Who listens to their wife? You gotta listen to me.
我们得去宗教用品店一趟
We gotta go down to the religious supply store.
买两加仑圣水
We gotta get ourselves a couple of gallons of holy water.
我表哥是牧师 可以帮我们打折
My cousin is a priest. He can get us a deal.
- 然后我们去跳蚤市场 - 我不想听
- Then we gotta go to the market. - I don't want to hear this.
- 买一大串大蒜 - 我不要听
- We gotta get big strings of garlic. - I'm not gonna listen.
- 我们要弄一些新鲜的羊血 - 我不要听
- We gotta get some fresh lamb's blood. - I'm not going to hear this.
雷 你要他们绑架你的家人
Ray, do you want 'em to take your family, kidnap 'em...
拿出肝脏做魔鬼饼吗?
tear their livers out and make some satanic pate?
我不要听 我不要听
I'm not going to hear this. I'm not going to listen.
雷 你在唸经
Ray, you're chanting. Ray.
雷 你在无意识的念经
Ray, look. Ray. Unconscious chanting. You're chanting.
我要杀死每个人
I want to kill everyone.
撒旦是好人 撒旦是朋友
Satan is good. Satan is our pal.
雷 你在念经
Ray, Ray, you're chanting. Hey.
一旦被他们控制住 一切就完了
Once they get in here, it's over, pal.
恶魔崇拜者?
Satanists, huh?
仪式杀人狂?
Ritual killers?
非常好
Nice. Very, very nice.
让我把事情搞清楚
So let me get this straight.
柯罗佩把瓦特当成祭品献给魔王?
The Klopeks are offering up Walter as a human sacrifice to Beelzebub?
这是一种说法
That's one of the theories. Yeah.
好极了
Mm-hmm. Great, great.
你就要这样在家里休息一周是吧?
So this is your relaxing week at home, huh?
我根本不会错过的
I wouldn't have missed this for the world.
- 约翰城的一周 - 你要去哪里?
- A week in Jonestown. - Where are you going?
厕所
To the bathroom.
别紧张
Relax.
是什么?
What is it?
卡罗?
Carol?
你请邻居来吃烤肉实在太好了
It was so nice of you to invite the new neighbours over for a barbecue.
撒旦是好人 撒旦是朋友
Satan is good. Satan is our pal.
我要杀死每个人
I want to kill everyone.
撒旦是好人 撒旦是朋友
Satan is good. Satan is our pal.
雷彼德森
Oh, Ray Peterson...
不管你做什么...
whatever you do...
都不要让他们对你做出...
don't let them do to you...
他们对我做的事
what they did to me.
我想那一定很痛
Ooh, I bet that hurts, huh?
这个鲜血奶昔是谁点的?
Who the heck ordered the blood shake?
雷 我是阿特 我只是假扮成史奇普
Hey, Ray. It's not Skip. It's me, Art. I'm just pretending to be Skip.
你在这理有没有看到冰钻?
You didn't happen to see an ice pick around here, did you?
别管闲事
Mind your own business.
Mind your own business!
我知道了!
Okay!
街坊美丽的一天
It's a beautiful day in this neighbourhood
It's a beautiful day for a neighbour
你是否愿意跟我在一起
Would you be mine Could you be mine
美丽街坊的和睦日
It's a neighbourly day in this beauty wood
美丽佳人的和睦日
A neighbourly day for a beauty
你是否愿意跟我在一起
Would you be mine Could you be mine
我总是想要你这样的邻居
I have always wanted to have a neighbour Just like you
我总是想要处在你的街坊
I've always wanted to live In the neighbourhood with you
让我们尽情享受美好的一天
So let's make the most of this beautiful day
既然我们在一起 我不如说
Since we're together I might as well say
你是否愿意跟我在一起
Would you be mine Could you be mine
你是否愿意做我邻居
Won't you be my neighbour
请你 请你
Won't you please Won't you please
做我邻居好吗
Please, won't you be my neighbour
雷 我们有个计划
Hey, Ray! Ray, we got a plan! Come on.
我们有个计划 快点下来
We got a plan. Come on. We got...
抱歉 我先生不舒服 他要留在房间里
Sorry, boys. My husband's not feeling well. He has to stay in his room.
- 他不乖 - 别这样
- Ooh, he was bad. - Come on.
卡罗 让他出来
Please, Carol, let him come out.
拜托
Come on.
在他变回我丈夫之前是不会出门的
He can't come out until he resembles the man that I married.
- 我们没有那么多时间 - 请让他出来
- We don't have that kind of time. - Please let him come out.
我已经把答案告诉你们了
I think that I have given you my answer.
不 蜜蜂从那里出来
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. The bees came from there.
- 小心这个洞 - 我们试试侧门
- Watch this hole. - Okay, let's try the side door.
好 做吧
Okay, do it.
做什么? 我们说好一起做的
Do what? We agreed to do it together.
雷
Ray. Ray.
我只是想打个盹
I'm only trying to take a nap.
我只是躺在这里闭上眼睛
I'm only laying here with my eyes closed...
想要睡他妈的一觉
trying to get some goddam sleep.
安静点 如果不重要我也不会吵醒你
Quiet, quiet, quiet. I wouldn't wake you if it wasn't important.
- 我们让柯罗佩现形了 - 知道了
- I think we flushed 'em out. The Klopeks. - Okay.
- 伦斯菲和我让他们现行了 - 怎么说?
- Rumsfield and I, we flushed 'em out. - How?
我们写了一张纸条塞在门下
We wrote a note. We slipped it under their door.
- 按了门铃然后遛之大吉 - 你这样做了?
- We rang the bell, and then we ran. - You did that?
- 是阿 - 老天! 蠢蛋
- Yeah. - Oh, geez! Stupid idi...
我真不敢相信
I can't believe you...
我只是写 "我知道你们干的好事"
All I did was write, "I know what you've done."
- 我又没有签名什么的 - 我真无法... 你这个蠢蛋
- I didn't sign it or anything. - Oh, I can't... You stupid...
- 你为什么不... 老天! - 你得吓唬吓唬他们
- Why didn't you... God! - You gotta goose these people.
你得给他们一点颜色 让他们知道你在这里
You gotta give them a little shot, let 'em know that you're there.
乖狗 文森 去捡吧
Good dog, Vince. Go get it.
阿特 你知道吗? 他们会认为是我写的
Here's the thing, Art. They're gonna think I did it.
- 为什么? - 那个老傢伙看到我在写纸条...
- Why? - The old guy saw me write a note...
把它放在瓦特的门底下
and put it under Walter's door.
所以他们会认为是我干的!
So they're gonna think that I did it!
你写了一张纸条放在... 我不知道
You wrote a note and put it under the... I didn't know that.
没关係 反正我门佔上风了
It doesn't matter 'cause we got 'em on the run now.
现在他们知道我们晓得了
Now they know that we know that they know that we know!
当然有关係 事情是你做的 可是他们会怀疑我!
Yes, it does matter! You did it, but they're gonna suspect me!
他们不会怀疑别人
They're not gonna suspect anybody. They're...
- 你知道这是什么吗? - 是一根骨头
- Do you know what this is? - It's a bone.
- 是股骨 - 是一根股骨
- It's a femur. - It's a femur bone.
股骨是人类的臀部骨头
A femur just happens to be a human thigh bone, Ray.
- 等等 你怎么知道? - 上生物课时学的
- Wait, how do you know that? - Biology 101.
看看这玩意的尺寸
Look at the size of this thing.
你想这是鸡骨头吗?
Think this came off a chicken or something?
文森从哪里挖到的?
Where the hell did Vince get this?
从篱笆下面挖的
He dug it up from underneath the fence.
雷 毫无疑问了
Ray. Ray, there's no doubt any more.
这是真的 你的邻居杀了人
This is real. Your neighbours are murdering people.
他们把尸体剁开 埋在后院里
They're chopping 'em up. They're burying 'em in their backyard.
雷 这是瓦特的骨头
Ray, this is Walter.
不!
No!
一定还有其他解释
There's just got to be some other explanation for this.
只是垃圾罢了 那傢伙到处捡垃圾
It's just some litter. The guy's a litterbug.
可能是糖果纸 可能是纸巾
It could be a candy bar wrapper. It could be a napkin.
可能是弄皱的信用卡收据
It could be a crumpled up credit card receipt.
那些东西满街都是
Those things blow around all the time.
不 是我的纸条
It, uh... No, it's my note.
- 噢! 抱歉
- Oh! Oh, I'm sorry.
我没看见你
I didn't see you. I didn't see you.
好极了 捏碎了啤酒罐你觉得好一些了吗?
Great. Crush a beer can. You feel better now?
我认为...
Well...
我们不应该再像幼稚园小朋友了
I think it's time we all stopped acting like kindergartners.
- 你说是不是 雷? - 是的 卡罗
- Don't you, Ray? - Yes, Carol.
在有人从屋顶跌下来或让自己着火之前
Now, before somebody falls off a roof or sets themselves on fire...
我们应该过去敲门
I think we should go over there, knock on their door...
邀请他们好好聊一聊
and invite ourselves in for a nice, neighbourly chat.
我们一个月前就该这么做了
Get to know these people like we should have done a month ago.
好主意 我来烤巧克力饼干
That's a good idea. I'll make brownies.
- 好极了 趁你们... - 我们不会邀你的
- Great. While you keep 'em busy, I... - You're not invited.
- 卡罗 我们明天再做好吗? - 你放松好吗?
- Can't we do this tomorrow, Carol? - Would you relax?
我们只要聊个五分钟
We'll probably find out more in five minutes of friendly chat...
可能就比你们一个月的案中侦查还有更多发现
than you guys can in a month of snooping around.
好 每个人尽量保持正常
Okay, now, everybody just act normal.
是谁?
Who is it?
我是隔壁的卡罗彼德森
It's Carol Peterson from next door.
巧克力饼干完了
There go the goddam brownies.
欢迎搬来到梅菲尔区 我们是你的邻居
Hi. Welcome to Mayfield Place. We're your neighbours.
我们带了一些点心
We brought dessert...
你妈妈在家吗?
Uh, is your mother home?
小伙子 拿去吧 吃些甜点
Here you go, sonny. A little something for the sweet tooth.
你们搬来一个月了
I can't believe you've lived here a whole month...
我们竟然还没过来打招呼
and we haven't come by to say hello.
我是你的邻居 雷彼德森 这是我太太 卡罗
I'm your neighbour, Ray Peterson. That's my wife, Carol.
这是邦妮 这是...
That's Bonnie, and this is, uh...
伦斯菲
Rumsfield's the name.
没听到你的名字 小伙子
Don't think I caught yours, sonny.
- 汉斯 - 汉斯
- Hans. - Hans.
基督徒的好名字 汉斯克里斯徒安徒生
A fine, Christian name. Hans Christian Andersen.
你是天主教徒吗?
What, are you Catholic?
我不知道
I don't know.
漂亮的姑娘
Oh. Pretty girl.
- 你的朋友吗? - 不 跟相框一起买的
- Friend of yours? - No, it came with the frame.
- 跟相框一起买的? - 是的
- "It came with the frame"? - Yes.
这是餐厅吗? 你吓了我一跳
Oh, is this the dining room? Oh! You startled me.
- 我叔叔鲁本 - 幸会
- My Uncle Reuben. - How do you do?
你就是住在隔壁的人
You are the one who lives next door.
- 我们来点咖啡如何? - 我来泡
- Um... why don't we get some coffee? - I'll do it.
我们坐下来聊聊好吗 鲁本?
What do you say we all sit down for a little face-to-face, eh, Reub?
他们在里面 大家都站着
They're in there, all right. They're just standing around.
好极了 别担心 我可以应付的
Oh, great. Don't worry, you guys. I can get this.
- 我真的很感谢你们的帮忙 - 没问题 小心点就是了
- I really appreciate your help. Really. - No problem. Just be careful.
保护网满危险的
It's pretty dangerous with the trip wire.
谢谢你的忠告
Thanks for your advice.
- 小心! - 当心!
- W-Watch! - Be careful!
- 我有注意 - 你没事吧?
- I'm watchin'. - Did you make it?
我没事
I'm all right. I'm okay, I'm okay.
把工具丢过来
Just throw me the tools.
今天真潮湿
Sure was damp today.
是啊 头发怎么弄都不对
Yes, I just can't seem to do anything with my hair.
吃点沙丁鱼吗?
A sardine?
我正在想少吃一点
I'm trying to cut back.
要来点沙丁鱼吗?
Sardine?
你们觉得星克立丘怎么样?
So, how are you enjoying Hinkley Hills?
我们都很喜欢
We just love it.
- 对吧? - 对
- Don't we? - Yes.
柯罗佩 这是斯拉夫文吗?
Klopek. What is that, Slavic?
不是
No!
鲁本 压力量表大概在第九级
About a nine on the tension scale, Reub.
你们目前还住得惯吗?
How do you like living here so far?
相当舒服的房子吧
Pretty comfortable house, ain't it?
牆壁很坚固
Good, solid walls.
地板也很坚固
Good, solid floors.
鲁本 有人被绑在地窖里吧?
Got somebody tied up in the old cellar, have you, Reub?
是灰尘的关係 抱歉
It's packing dust. I'm sorry.
所以...
So...
就你和叔叔住在这里 是吗?
Just you and Unc living here in the house, is that it, sonny?
- 不... - 这是一个小家庭
- No... - Please, this is a small family:
我 这个小伙子
Me, the young boy...
还有我哥哥 他是医生
and my brother... the doctor.
社区里有个医生真好
Won't it be nice to have a doctor in the neighbourhood?
你们能保留这些原木实在太好了
You know, I think it's great you've been able to stay with all the original wood.
纳普斯一家住在这里时 我从来没拜访过
I was never over here when the Knapps lived here.
那对纳普斯家实在太遗憾了
How unfortunate for the Knapps.
说来好笑 可是我不记得门口有看到搬家的卡车
You know, it's funny, but I don't remember seeing a moving van out front.
这我不明白 但卡车一整天都停在户外
I don't understand that. It was parked outside all day!
怎么样...
S-Say, how is, uh...
你这里的下水道管用吗?
the... drainage on your property here?
在我们家 只要一下雨
I know when it rains at our house...
地下室就会淹水
boy, the basement just floods right over.
地下室? 雷提出一个好主意
Basement? Ray comes up with a winning idea.
也许我们应该看看地下室
Maybe we should go take a look in the basement.
也许几分钟前是哥哥在那里
Maybe that was brother down there tapping on the ceiling a couple minutes ago.
谁晓得?
Who knows?
你哥哥是什么样的医生?
Just what kind of doctor is this brother of yours?
你何不自己去问他?
Why don't you ask him yourself?
啊 我们有客人
Ah, we have guests.
可以这么说
Sort of.
我哥哥 医生
My brother, the doctor.
华纳柯罗佩
Werner Klopek.
幸会
How nice to meet you.
雷彼德森
Ray Peterson.
抱歉 我的手套
Oh, pardon my glove.
我认为蜡烛对女士很浪漫
I thought the candles would be romantic... for the ladies.
它们很美
They're lovely.
我真的为油漆感到抱歉
I really must apologize for the paint.
我正在修饰我的油画
I was just touching up one of my pictures.
绘画能让我放轻松
I find painting relaxes me.
- 要代糖吗? - 不用 谢谢
- Sugar substitute? - No, thank you.
我们没有早点介绍自己实在太失礼了
It was impolite of us not to have introduced ourselves sooner.
我的工作相当孤独
I find my work is rather solitary.
总是使我们一再搬家
It always keeps us on the move.
你知道我们四年内搬了四次吗?
Did you know we've had to move four times in as many years?
搬家一定让你不好受吧 汉斯
Oh, all that moving must be very hard on you, Hans.
确实 明天...
Indeed. And tomorrow...
我们必须到大学讨论另一次搬家
Tomorrow we must all go to the university to discuss yet another transfer.
不 我们才刚刚认识你们
No. And we're just getting to know you.
真遗憾 是不是 亲爱的?
That's a shame. Isn't that a shame, honey?
很遗憾
That's a shame.
谁说的?
Says who?
我今天才跟汉斯说 今天
And I was just remarking to Hans... today...
若能认识我们所有的新邻居该有多好
how nice it would be to meet all of our new neighbours...
而你们就来了
and here you are.
- 事实上 我们没有全到 - 是吗?
- Actually, we're not all here. - Oh?
瓦特 隔壁的老人 我们不知道他到哪里去了
Walter, the old man next door. We don't know where the hell he is.
天啊!
Oh, God! Jesus Christ!
抱歉!
Sorry! Sorry! Ow!
老人的困境
Terrible thing, the plight of the elderly.
我们前天还在说
We were just remarking the other day...
像那种老人
about how an old guy like that...
可能不声不响就翘辫子了
could just drop off the face of the Earth without a sign.
消失了 没有人再看到他 毫无踪迹
Vanish. No one ever see him again. No trace. Nothing.
雷 对吧? 我们昨天还谈到
Right, Ray? Yesterday, wasn't it? We were just talking about it yesterday.
我猜你们有
I bet you were.
我们别再说客套话了
Why don't we just cut all this polite crap, all right?
你们每次传出来的噪音到底是怎么回事?
What's the weird goddam noise you got comin' outta here all the time?
我想我们应该走...
Uh, I think we should go...
地窖里到底藏了什么 柯罗佩先生?
What have you got in the cellar, Herr Klopek?
- 马克 - 雷
- Mark! - Ray.
来吧 告诉他你看到什么
Come on. Tell him what you saw. Tell him.
我必须借一下洗手间
I have to use your bathroom.
雷 还记得前天晚上吗?
Ray, remember night before last?
- 你说他们在挖地 - 别开门!
- You said they were digging. - Don't open that!
雷!
Ray!
你把马养在地下室?
You keep a horse in the basement?
- 那是窃贼吗? - 不 是阿特
- Is it a burglar? - No, it's Art.
另一位邻居?
Another neighbour?
是个胖子
A fat one.
走啊 你这个卑劣的杂种
Go on, you mangy mutt!
如果蓝卓吓到你们 我很抱歉
I'm sorry if Landru frightened you.
它的尺寸常会吓到人 - 噢 不会
- His size tends to overwhelm people. - Oh, no, no.
我们打扰太久了 很高兴认识你们
We've imposed on you enough for one evening. It's been lovely meeting you.
- 医生 鲁本 再见 - 再见 汉斯
- See you, Doc. Later, Reub. - Bye, Hans.
医生 谈得真愉快
Yes, Doctor. It's been real.
- 你还好吧? - 我没事
- Are you all right? - Yes, I'm fine.
让我们很快再聚聚
Let's do this again sometime... real soon.
- 我们自己回去吧 亲爱的? - 晚安
- We'll see ourselves to the door. Honey? - Goodnight.
好吧 我承认他们是有点奇怪
Okay, I admit it. They're slightly eccentric.
- 何止有点奇怪 - 卡罗...
"Slightly eccentric"? -Carol...
- 但这不代表... - 拜托!
- But that doesn't mean... - Come on!
这些人根本变态
These people are clearly psychos!
雷 你认为呢?
Ray, what do you think?
是呀 你觉得呢?
Yeah, what do you think?
雷 你怎么一声不吭
Right. Been awfully quiet, Ray.
发表一下意见吧
Maybe we could have a little participation here.
我认为他们没问题 我想邦妮和卡罗是对的
I think they're clean. I think Bonnie and Carol are right.
- 看吧? - 好极了 雷
- See? - That's great, Ray.
只想讨好女人而不给我们撑腰
Just pull open the door, pull the rip cord and bail out on us.
还亏是你先开始的
That's rich, considering you're the one who started this whole thing.
喂 是谁先开始的?
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Who started it, tuna neck?
整件事都是你挑起的
You instigated this whole damn thing!
你知道事谁挑起的吗? 是你儿子看到别人在后院挖地
You know who instigated this? Your boy watching people dig in the backyard!
- 你给我离开... - 亲爱的 我们可以失陪一下吗?
- You leave my... - Honey, would you and Bonnie excuse us?
我应该在起居室跟兄弟们谈一下
I think I should have a talk with the boys in the den for a few minutes.
好
Okay.
亲爱的 看到你回复神智真好
It's good to see you've come to your senses, sweetie.
只要一两分钟
Just a minute or two.
雷 怎么样?
So, what's the deal, Ray?
你跟婆子们站在同一国是吗?
Are you siding with the chicks against us? Is that it?
是呀 你完全让女人摆布?
Yeah, are you totally pussy-whipped or what?
有种就挺身站出来
Just take your balls out of your wife's purse.
难得表明一下你的立场
Make a stand for one time in your life.
雷 别这样
Hey, Ray, come on.
- 只是打个比方 - 是笑话 他在开玩笑
- It's just a figure of speech. - It's a joke. He's kiddin' around.
是瓦特的假发
Oh, it's Walter's rug.
你拿到老头的假发了 不得了
You got an old guy's wig. Big deal.
你整天都把它塞在裤子里吗?
You've had that in your trousers all day?
你昨天在瓦特家找到之后
After you found this in Walter's house yesterday...
我把它塞回信箱里了
I slipped it back in through the mail slot.
这一次是从哪里来的?
Where did you get it this time?
柯罗佩家? 哇赛
Klopeks? Wow.
狗从地下室冲出来的时候
After the dog came up out of the basement.
我发现它塞在一堆杂志中间
I found it wedged between a bunch of magazines...
杂志都是寄给瓦特的
all of which were addressed to Walter.
那意思就是说...
Then that means that...
柯罗佩潜回瓦特家里...
Klopeks went back inside Walter's house...
拿到假发
and got the hair.
士兵 我们该怎么办?
What do we do now, soldier?
你听到他们说明天要出们
You heard them say they were going away tomorrow.
早上等车子一开走...
As soon as that car leaves in the morning...
我就要跳过篱笆 找不到尸体誓不回来
I'm going over the fence and I'm not comin' back 'til I find a dead body.
没有人能干掉我街上的老人还逍遥法外
Nobody knocks off an old man in my neighbourhood and gets away with it.
各位 我们全副警戒
Gentlemen, we are on alert.
亲爱的 你知道可以做什么吗?
Honey, you know what you could do?
去园艺中心买些石板铺在走道上
Go get those flag stones at the garden centre and put them along the walk.
那是一件好差事
Yeah, that'd be a nice project.
可是我今天要和阿特打一个半小时的四人二球赛
I've got a foursome lined up with Art today in an hour and a half though.
我又不是说马上 你讨厌高尔夫的
I didn't mean right now. You hate golf.
我在休假 我只想出去透透气
Well, it's my vacation. I just wanted to get out of the house.
被我烦了一星期 你应该也想出去兜兜风
I would think, after the week I put you through, you'd want to too.
为什么我觉得你想摆脱我?
Why do I get the impression you're trying to get rid of me?
我要出去一整天 这是你去拜访艾芙琳的好机会
I'm gonna be gone all day. It'd be a good time for you to go see Evelyn.
跟表弟妹好好玩
And you have a good time with the cousins.
我讨厌他们 鲁迪是白痴 黛安好臭
I hate them, Dad. Rudy is a moron, and Diane smells.
周末愉快
Have a nice weekend.
回头见
I'll see you later.
卡罗 看我的新高尔夫手套
Hey, Carol, see my new golf glove?
这样我打高尔夫就不会起水泡了
I got it so I don't get blisters playing golf.
我们真的要大打特打
We're gonna be playing that much golf. Really.
前面当心
Fore!
你认为她相信吗?
Think she bought it?
史帝夫 怎么样?
Yo, Steve-man. What's the haps, dude?
你今天一定要过来 保证精彩
You gotta come down here today. It's gonna be live.
不 你一定要来
No, you've got to.
有大事要发生 我不能告诉你
Something's about to happen. I can't tell you.
你知道你在干什么吗 阿特?
Are you sure you know what you're doing, Art?
那些电线里面都是电
There's a lot of juice going through those wires.
要是碰错了 你就烤熟了
You hit the wrong one, you're a Post Toastie.
电力是我的朋友
Electricity is our friend.
何况 我们要摘掉他们的警铃
Besides, we wanna take out their alarms, don't we?
也许我们可以避开篱笆另外找条路
I was thinking we could bypass the fence altogether and find another way in.
没有人知道他们有多少警铃
No one knows how many trip alarms they have in there.
不 我只要喀擦一声就可以全部摆平
No, I can take out everything they've got with one clip of the snips.
- 是吧 队长? - 肯定
- Right, Captain? - Affirmative.
警铃模式
Siren mode.
很酷吧?
Pretty neat, eh?
我可以连接所有警铃频道
I can raise all the police channels...
和电力公司频道
and the power company channels on this baby.
- 阿特 小心点 - 没问题的 雷
- Be careful up there, Art. - It's okay, Ray.
我们得赶紧行动才行 我们正在耗时间
We gotta get going though. We're burning daylight here.
我们过去后 应该从哪里挖起?
Hey, where should we start diggin' once we get over there?
从后院开始 然后检查地下室
We start in the backyard, then check the basement.
上面小心点 慢慢来
Be careful up there. Go slow, huh?
安全是我的中间名
Hey, safety is my middle name.
我以为他的中间名是路易
I thought his middle name was Louis.
你确定你没问题吗?
Are you sure you're all right up there?
他知道自己在干麻吗?
I don't know that he knows what he's doing.
- 那你为什么不上去? - 太高了
- Well, why didn't you go up there? - It's very high.
天哪!
Oh, Jesus!
老天 快用那玩意叫救护车
Jesus Christ! Get an ambulance on that thing!
我没事
I'm okay. I'm all right.
我触电了 可是没事
I took a jolt, but I'm okay.
你能站起来吗?
Can you stand up?
- 试试这个 - 好多了
- Try one of these. - Oh, yeah, that's better.
老天
No, no, no. Jesus.
看我的手指
Look at my fingers.
指甲都变黑了
My fingernails are black.
- 我补的牙好热 - 看看这
- My fillings are hot. - Hey, look at this.
他还真切对了线路 警铃没响
The man actually hit the right wire. There's no alarm.
- 干得好 - 恭喜
- Hey, good work. - Congratulations
- 我要去建立通讯基地了 祝一切顺利 - 好的
- I'm gonna set up a communications base. - You got it.
拿去 你需要这个
Here, you're gonna need this.
伦斯菲 老兄
Hey, hey, hey, Rumsfield! Dude!
你拿着枪做什么?
What are you doing with the gun?
闭上你的狗嘴 漆你他妈的房子
Just shut up and paint your goddam house!
哇赛 好
Whoa! Fine.
特遣部队一号 这是鹰眼
Task Force One, this is Eagle Eye.
一切安全
You are all clear.
收到了 鹰眼 我们正要跨过去
Roger, Eagle Eye. We're going over.
收到了 红罗浮 让雷跨过去
Roger. Red rover, red rover, let Ray go over.
很好 现在 红罗浮 让阿特跨过去
Good. Now, red rover, red rover, let Art go on over.
好极了 结束
That's great. Over.
天气变得好热
It's really getting hot out here.
是啊 变得好热
Yeah. Yeah, it is getting hot, Art.
你怎么不挖个自己的洞?
Why don't you dig one of your own holes, huh?
我只是在检查这个 而且... 无线电... 我在监督
I was just checking this one. Besides, the radio... I was monitoring...
事情远比我们想得还棘手
This is turning out to be a lot more work than we thought it was gonna be.
我们进屋吧 里面应该比较凉快
Why don't we check the house? It's probably a lot cooler in there.
好主意 让我们试试屋子
That's a good idea.Let's try the house.
从地下室开始
We'll start in the basement.
我们从地下室开始 然后一路往上
We'll start in the basement and just work our way up.
雷 我想我们在后院找不到东西的原因
Ray, I'm thinking the reason we didn't find anything in the backyard...
是因为他们可能没有把尸体埋在后院
is because they probably weren't burying anybody in the backyard.
他们把尸体挖起来埋在地下室
They were digging bodies up and they probably buried them in the basement.
只是可能而已 阿特
That's a possibility, Art.
我们从厨房开始吧 那里可能有些冰啤酒
I say we start in the kitchen. They probably got some cold beer in there.
或是德国蒜肠什么的 我饿死了
Or some knockwurst or something. I'm starving.
门锁了
It's locked.
把信用卡给我 -
Hey, give me a credit card.
- 你从哪里学的? - 我不知道怎么弄
- Where did you learn how to do that? - I don't know how to do this.
反正是一张烂卡
Ah, it's a shit store anyway.
雷 你知道什么是 "擅闯空门" 吗?
Ray, do the words "breaking and entering" mean anything to you?
伦斯菲先生 嘿!
Hey, Mr Rumsfield! Hey, yo, man!
我想向你介绍我的朋友
I wanted to introduce you to my friend.
- 史帝夫昆兹 - 嘿 老兄
- This is Steve Kuntz. - Hey, dude.
他今天下午过来看好戏
He's here to watch the show this afternoon.
很好
Great.
嘿 老兄 好戏什么时候开始?
Hey, man, when's the big unveiling, huh?
- 我两小时候要去工作 - 嘿 老兄 滚开
- I gotta go to work in a couple hours. - Hey, man, piss off!
把这个浑小子撵出你的院子
Get this lame-o out of your yard!
- 混小子 滚出我的院子 - 怎么搞的?
- Get out of my yard, lame-o! Hey! - What's his problem?
滚出我的院子
Get out of my yard!
雷 看看暖炉的尺寸
Ray, look at the size of this furnace.
这玩意一定有八十年历史了
This thing's got to be 80 years old.
这种老房子一定很难取暖
These old places have got to be hell to heat.
这栋房子没有那么大
This house isn't that big.
要这种暖炉做什么?
What the hell does he need a furnace like this for?
一定做过修改 导管是新的
I think there's been some modifications on this 'cause this conduit's brand new.
它一直通到后面那里 然后从天花板的洞穿过去
It runs all the way back over there and up through a hole in the ceiling.
有一些通到他们客厅
I saw some of that in their living room.
家用暖炉的调温器
And a thermostat on a home furnace...
需要到五千度吗?
Is that supposed to go to 5,000 degrees, do you think?
那一定就是噪音的来源
It must be what all the noise was.
看看这里装的东西
Look at all the stuff they put together down here.
- 屋子里都是电池 - 少说有四十个
- They got this place wired with batteries. - There's got to be 40 of them.
你看 这里有电
Look, we got power here.
这不是普通的暖炉
This is no ordinary furnace.
那是什么?
What's that?
喂 伦斯菲!
Yo, Rumsfield!
不得了!
Awesome!
伦斯菲先生 你还好吗?
Mr Rumsfield, are you okay?
- 我没事 - 帅呆了
- Yes, yes, I'm all right. - That was very cool, man.
阿特 看
Art. Art, look.
- 你看! 我找到了 - 松脱的土
- Look! I found it! - That's loose dirt.
他们一定在暖炉里烧尸体
They must have burned his body up in the furnace...
然后把他的骨头埋在这里
and then buried his bones right here.
现在我们该怎么办?
What do we do now?
我会告诉马克这里有个火葬场
I'll tell him that they built a crematorium down here.
别告诉他 他会想跑下来看 等我们找到端倪再说
Don't tell him that. He'll just want to come down. Wait 'til we find something.
雷 那可能要一整晚
Ray, that could take all night.
伦斯菲先生 你们让整条街停电了
Mr Rumsfield, you guys managed to knock out the power in the entire block.
搞不好整个城镇南端都停电
Probably the whole south end of town.
瑞奇 给我闭嘴!
Ricky, shut up!
我们要去麦当劳
We're gonna make a run to McD's.
- 你要来个麦当堡什么的吗? - 不行!
- You want a Quarterpounder or something? - Oh, no way!
你们现在不能走 精彩好戏就要上场了
Hey, you guys can't go now. It's the best part.
- 我打给送披萨的 - 好耶!
- I called the pizza dude. - All right!
雷 我想我们可以放弃了 他们不可能埋的这么深
Ray, I think we can give up. They'd never bury him this deep.
除了我们之外 谁会一直挖到这团烂泥?
Who, besides us, would dig this deep into this kind of sludge?
那是金属!
That was metal!
你碰到地窖了!
That was metal! You hit a crypt!
他们把他埋在地窖里! 我去拿喷灯! 我打给它
They buried him in a crypt! I'll get my blowtorch! I'll call it in!
喂! 呃... 鹰眼 这是特遣部队一号
Hello! Hey, uh... Eagle Eye, this is Ground Force One.
我们找到瓦特了 我马上来!
We have found Walter! We found Walter! I'll be out in a minute!
快挖! 太棒了! 我们找到他了
Dig there! Dig there! Oh, yes! We found him!
我们逮到你了 鲁本
We caught you, Reub.
你把我们当成傻子 可是你错了
You've been playing us for saps, but you were wrong.
韦嘉纳先生! 阿特!
Mr Weingartner! Art!
看那边! 现在就看!
Look! Look over there! Look! Right now!
走开 走开 我自己来
Go on. Go on. I'll...
瓦特!
Walter!
雷! 雷蒙!
Ray! Raymond!
仔细听好 先生
Listen up real carefully, mister.
我们碰到大麻烦了
We got a real problem.
雷 你猜我看到谁了? 是瓦特
Hey, Ray, guess who's not in the basement? Walter!
他回来了!
He's back! He's back!
柯罗佩回来了 还带着警察
Klopeks! With coppers!
拦住他们 我去找雷
Keep 'em busy. Keep 'em busy. I'll get Ray.
- 拦着他们! - 好的 没问题
- Keep them busy! - All right, okay, all right!
停车! 停啊! 别往前了!
Stop! Stop right there! Don't go any further!
我叫你停啊 停!
You're going! Stop!
警察先生 等等
Hey, Mr Officer, wait.
这些人在我爸妈家
There are these people in my parents' house...
把他们的食物吃光了!
and they're eating all their food!
雷 瓦特回来了
Ray, Walter showed up!
- 还有柯罗佩 我叫瑞奇去... - 我挖到瓦斯管了 快跑!
- The Klopeks! I got Ricky down there... - I hit the gas line! Run!
- 瓦斯! - 快跑!
- Gas!  - Run!
- 这里出了什么事? - 谢天谢地
- What is the problem here? - Thank God you're here.
- 没问题 警官 - 这不是警察的事
- No problem, sir. - This is not a police matter.
我们挖到瓦斯管 瓦斯管外洩!
We hit a pipe! There's all kinds of gas!
要爆炸了!
It's gonna blow!
- 棒呆了 - 瑞奇真知道怎么搞派对
- All right! - Ricky sure knows how to throw a party.
那是你的房子?
Was that your house?
雷
Ray.
那里有东西在动
Something is moving in there.
雷 你找到了 对吧?
Ray... Ray, you found it, right?
在爆炸之前你找到了 对吧?
Before it blew, you found it, right?
告诉我你找到了 对不对?
Hey, tell me you found it. You found it, right?
在一切爆炸之前你一定找到了
Before everything went off, you had to have found it.
先生 你有官司上身了
You got a lawsuit on your hands, mister.
天哪 怎么回事?
Oh, God, what's this?
请注意 远离路障
Your attention, please. Please stay behind the barricade.
请退后
You want to step back, please?
- 那是我家 - 抱歉 我得获得瓦斯公司批准
- That's my house. - Sorry. I've got to get the all clear from the gas company.
- 我可以批准 她住这里 - 我有问你吗?
- I can clear this. She lives here. - Did I ask you?
小姐 请后退 听到没?
- 亲爱的 他们把你怎么了? - 你剪了头发
我喜欢
警官 那栋房子埋了一具尸体
- 叫斯尼克的老人 对吧? - 对 坐在这里的这个老人...
- 被埋在那间房子里 - 小心点
- is buried in that house, Sherlock. - Watch it.
他到底跑哪去了?
Where was he anyway?
斯尼克先生今晚八点以前都在医院里
Mr Seznick was at the hospital 'til 8:00 this evening.
星期一晚上他心悸了
Monday night he had some heart palpitations.
他打电话给女儿和女婿 他们把他送到医院
He called his daughter and son-in-law, and they took him to the hospital.
那假发呢? 他们在房子里找到假发
What about the wig? They found a wig in this house.
- 他的假发 - 柯罗佩帮他收信
- His wig. - The Klopeks were picking up his mail.
医生可能把假发跟报纸及信件混在一起了
The doctor somehow got that wig mixed up with the newspapers and letters.
医生? 你真相信他是医生?
"Doctor"? You don't believe that this guy's a real doctor, do you?
对 我相信他是医生
Yes, I do believe he's a doctor.
事实上 他是一位受人尊敬的病理学家
In fact, he's a very well-respected pathologist, my friend.
你没有让他在那场爆炸丧生算你走运了
I'd say that you are damn lucky you didn't kill him in that blast.
是阿 谢天谢地
Oh, yeah, I thank my lucky stars.
- 好好照顾这个煳涂蛋 - 老兄 你的车抱歉了
- Take care of this nitwit. - Sorry about your car, man.
破坏私人财产 破坏公共财产
Destruction of private property. Destruction of public property.
三起刑事侵入罪
Three counts of criminal trespassing.
骚扰 攻击 破坏
Harassment, assault, vandalism.
那个老人还说他收到勒赎信
And that poor old man claims he's got a ransom note...
说你绑架他的狗
that says you kidnapped his dog!
你听得见吗 彼得森先生?
Do you hear me okay, Mr Peterson?
我真的喜欢你的发型
I really do like your hair, honey.
这不会改变事实
You know, this doesn't change a thing.
他们以为没事了 但可不是这样
They may think it does. They may think they're off the hook, but they're not.
他们有事 对吧? 告诉他们
No, they're not. Are they, Ray? Go ahead, tell 'em.
我们掌握了他们犯罪的证据
We got the goods on 'em, don't we?
哪一天他们去挖那个院子
Someday they're gonna dig up the back of that yard...
会发现股骨之外的整块残骸
and they're gonna find the rest of that skeleton to go with that femur.
- 可能不是瓦特 但... - 闭嘴 阿特!
- It might not be Walter, but... - Shut up, Art! Shut up!
天啊 你还不知道要罢手
God, you don't know when to quit, do you?
看看我!
Look at me!
都是因为你 我去掉半条命
I'm a shell of a man because of you, Art.
- 好了 - 士兵!
- Now, now... - Soldiers!
你别再去烦他们了!
You leave 'em alone! Get off their case already!
他们又没有对我们怎么样
They didn't do anything to us. They didn't do anything to us!
好吧 他们是不一样 他们独来独往
All right, so they're different! So they keep to themselves!
你能怪他们吗? 隔壁邻居闯进他们家里
Can you blame them? They live next door to people who break into their house...
在他们出门时把房子烧掉了
and burn it down while they're gone for the day.
还记得你说住在郊区的人吗?
Remember what you were saying about people in the 'burbs?
像史奇普的人
People like Skip?
锄了八百次的草后突然变了样
People who mow their lawn for the 800th time and then snap?
那就是我们! 不是他们!
Well, that's us! It's not them! That's us!
是我们跳过篱笆 偷窥别人的窗户
We're the ones vaulting over fences and peeking in through people's windows!
是我们把垃圾扔到街上 是我们点的火
We're the ones throwing garbage in the street and lighting fires!
是我们自己疑神疑鬼
We're the ones who are acting suspicious and paranoid, Art!
我们才是疯子! 不是他们!
We're the lunatics! Us! It's not them!
是我们
It's us.
我不知道要怎么说
I don't know what to say.
你要我搬家吗?
What, do you want me to move?
- 我要杀了他! - 你疯了!
- I'm gonna kill him! - You're crazy!
- 退后! -  住手!
- Back off! - Stop it! Stop it!
分开!
Break it up!
- 住手! - 我不管! 我被炸到了!
- Stop it! Stop it! - I don't care! I've been blown up!
带我去医院!
Take me to the hospital!
带我去医院 我不舒服
Take me to a hospital. I'm sick.
我的眼睛很痛
My eye hurts.
亲爱的 我会找出他们送你去哪家医院
Honey? I'll just find out what hospital they're taking you to...
然后我随后就到
and then I'll... follow right along.
-好吗? - 好的
- Okay? - Okay, honey.
- 你还好吧? 我很好 卡罗
- You okay? - Yeah, I'm fine, Carol.
混小子 离开我的车
Okay, hepcats, get off my car!
老兄 你应该待久一点
Dude, you should hang out a little bit.
送披萨的马上就来了
We've got the pizza dude coming.
你这个白痴 呆子
You imbecile! You sub-moron, you!
是谁?
Who's that?
柯罗佩医生 很抱歉
Oh, Dr Klopek, I'm so sorry.
柯罗佩医生 等我出狱后
You know, Dr Klopek, when I get out of prison...
我会帮你重盖新房子
I'm gonna help you rebuild your house.
我甚至会亲手盖一部分 我有工具
I'll even do some of the work myself. I have the tools.
卡罗父亲刚送给我一套新工具
Carol's father just gave me a brand new set of tools.
我看起来像白痴吗 彼德森先生
Do I look like an idiot, Mr Peterson?
不像
No.
你把我当成傻子吗?
Do you take me for an imbecile?
没有
No.
你骗得了别人
You may have fooled the others, Mr Peterson...
可是骗不了我
but you don't fool me.
我骗了别人?
Uh, I fooled the others?
- 可是你骗不了我 - 我骗不了你?
- But you don't fool me. - I don't?
对 你骗不了
No, you don't.
我不懂你的意思
Am I missing something, Doctor?
少装了 彼德森先生 你在我的地下室
Come now, Mr Peterson. You were in my basement.
你当然看了暖炉里面
Surely, you looked in the furnace.
我看到了暖炉 医生
I saw your furnace, Doctor...
可是我认为暖炉是自家的事
but I figured a man's furnace is his own business.
你看到一个骷髅头了 对吧?
You saw one of my skulls, didn't you?
我知道你有
Oh, yes. I know you did.
它属于你的邻居
It belonged to a neighbour of yours.
名叫纳普斯
The name was Knapp.
我们的房子是从他们那来的
We took the house from them.
我像他们出价买房子 可是你知道老人是什么样子
I offered to buy it, but you know how old people are.
他们恋旧 捨不得
They grow so attached to things.
柯罗佩医生 我忘了皮夹
Uh, you know, Dr Klopek, I think I forgot my wallet.
我让你留着股骨
I let you keep the femur.
可是骷髅头要还我
Now, now, I want my skull.
也许 我应该拿你的
Or, perhaps, I might just take yours.
汉斯
送披萨的!
干得好!
真够瞧
公民逮捕!
我 雷彼德森 因为你企图谋杀
我以公民的身分逮捕你
for my attempted murder!
这个人不知道自己在说什么
The man doesn't know what he's talking about.
- 公民逮捕 - 雷
- Citizen's arrest. Citizen's arrest. - Oh, Ray.
别惹我 卡罗 他承认他们杀了纳普斯一家人
Don't start with me, Carol. The man confessed. They murdered the Knapps.
- 他精神错乱 - 嘿 福尔摩斯
- He's demented. - Hey, Sherlock.
叫柯罗佩告诉你 他们把尸体埋在哪里
Get the Klopeks to tell you where they buried the stiffs.
你拿不出尸体 你没有证据
You don't have a stiff. You don't have any evidence.
现在有证据了
You do now.
这是你的车吗 柯罗佩医生?
This your vehicle, Dr Klopek?
医生 我们走吧
Let's go, Doc.
嘿! 小木偶!
Hey! Pinocchio!
你要去哪里?
Where are you going?
逮到你了!
Gotcha!
别动 小伙子
Don't you make a move, sonny.
我在丛林待过一年半 三两下就可以折断你的脖子
I was 18 months in the bush, and I can snap your neck in a heartbeat.
我认为全世界的变态和狂热者以及谋杀者
I think the message to psychos, fanatics, murderers...
都应该知道
nutcases all over the world is, uh...
别找郊区居民的麻烦 因为我们不会忍受的
do not mess with suburbanites because, uh, we're not gonna take it any more.
我们不是只会照顾草坪
We're not gonna be content to look after our lawns...
给汽车打蜡和油漆房子
and wax our cars, paint our houses.
我们会把他们揪出来
We're out to get 'em, Don. We are out to get them.
- 哈罗 - 嗨
- Hello. - Hi.
你现在要做什么?
So, what are you gonna do now?
我要打包去湖边
I'm gonna pack a bag and go up to the lake.
我们逮到他们了 邻居
We got 'em, neighbour.
- 我会避开他们 - 嘿 大伙儿
- Get away from him. - Hey, you guys.
想去喝杯啤酒什么的吗?
You wanna go down to Bowl-O-Rama for a beer or something?
那招窒息压制真够瞧 那傢伙真凶暴
Man, that was an incredible choke hold you put on me, pal. The guy's a brute.
那只手指还好吧?
How's that finger? Is it okay?
你们要去哪里?
Where are you guys going? Where you going?
去渡假
I'm going on vacation.
渡假? 你疯了吗?
"Vacation"? What, are you crazy?
这事成了媒体的头条新闻
This is a major media event here.
主持人瑞佛拉要来 他要去挖柯罗佩的地下室
Geraldo Rivera's coming, and he's gonna excavate the basement of the Klopeks!
它会在全世界实况卫星转播
It's gonna be broadcast on satellite all over the world, live!
阿特
Art!
你太太回来了
Your wife's home.
- 而且你的房子着火了! - 阿特 你在哪里?
- And your house is on fire! - Art, where are you?
我太太回来了
My wife is home!
彼德森先生 你要去哪里?
Mr Peterson, where you going?
好戏才刚刚开始呢
It's just starting to get good.
瑞奇 我要出门一阵子
I'm going away for a while, Ricky.
我要你帮我守一下街坊
I want you to keep an eye on the neighbourhood for me.
没问题 彼德森先生
You betcha, Mr Peterson.
包在我身上
No problem.
天啊 我真爱这条街
God, I love this street.